Our Secret
EP11
Let me tell you something.
Our city will hold a painting competition
a few days later,
which requires each school to recommend several students to participate.
If you wanna sign up,
Kong Shadi
just come here now to get the registration form.
Sir, Ding Xian can do it.
Yes, she can.
Sir, she can.
Here you are.
Ding Xian,
Can you do it?
Mom
How do you think about it?
It's quite good.
But
you are now in the second semester of high school.
If it were any other time, I would definitely allow you to do it.
But now is the critical time.
You must focus on your study.
Painting is just one of your hobbies.
Don't pay much attention to it.
OK.
Ding Xian,
I'm talking to you.
Don't give me that deep freeze.
You wouldn't agree anyway.
You talk to me in this attitude?
I do it all for your own good.
I won't be bad to you.
Mom, water cures anger.
Show me
your composition.
My family.
It's always noisy at home.
My mother is very similar to my sister.
They often get angry.
When something goes wrong with them,
they will speak very loudly,
loudly enough
to wake the dead.
That's what I am in your mind?
Speak loudly enough to wake the dead.
Good idiom.
Rewrite.
Why wouldn't she let me tell the truth?
Dad
I don't wanna get married in the future.
Hey, little boy.
I understand you.
Go rewrite it.
Don't hesitate.
Let me accompany you to sign up.
What's going on?
Please persuade her.
She doesn't wanna sign up for the painting competition.
I heard that Yang Chunzi also signed up.
Come on Little Monster.
Don't be afraid.
It is always good to participate.
Forget it, let me think again.
The class is about to start.
Don't be afraid.
Sit down.
Dad, why are you dressed like this?
I'm awesome this time.
Let me tell you.
Just play it by ear later.
Ding Wencheng
Does this look good on me?
Yes, you look good.
Well.
Is my lipstick too red?
Too red? No.
Xianxian,
do you think she is good-looking?
Yes.
Mom
You look good in this lipstick.
You are so beautiful today.
Where are you going?
Your dad follows the fashion.
He'll take me to the concert and eat western food.
I have never been to such a place.
We should also enjoy
the elegant life from time to time.
So I will cultivate our taste
with your mother and Congcong.
Good habits need to be developed
from an early age.
Xianxian, you just stay at home.
Don't worry, I'm not a child either.
Well.
Ding Juncong
Ding Juncong, hurry up.
Congcong, come here.
Let's go.
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
What's the matter?
I refuse to be with you.
I wanna watch cartoons at home.
Watch cartoons?
Don't be a good-for-nothing boy.
It's not easy for your dad to get tickets.
Right, these tickets are very expensive.
You must come with us.
Right, the concert is so good.
If I don't need to do my homework at home,
I'll also like to go. So you go.
That's your business. I won't go anyway.
Then stay at home!
Ding Xian, take care of him.
Let him do his homework, and I'll check when I come back.
Let's go.
Dad
That's all I can do for you.
Ding Wencheng
Hurry up.
Hello.
Come on.
Let me take you to the venue.
I may not be able to go.
Why?
OK.
Hello.
You two come here now.
Would you like some?
Put it there.
OK.
Juncong
It's such a fine day today.
Won't you go out?
I don't want to.
It's rare that mom and dad are not home.
You wanted to
go to that game center just the other day, right?
You can go there.
I'll keep your secret.
Don't think I don't know what you want.
I'm not going.
I just wanna piss you off.
Why are you here?
Let us help you take care of your brother.
You just feel free to participate in the competition.
I'm King of Children of Shen Hai High School.
Don't worry.
My brother is very...
Don't hesitate. Get ready.
-My Brother...  -Go.
Hurry up.
Hello bro.
Let me
stay with you today, okay?
What are you doing?
Don't look.
Oh, little boy.
Why can't I take a look?
What are you doing?
Show me, will you?
OK.
Let me stay with you today, okay?
So can you teach me
how to play this game?
OK.
This is my favorite game.
Wenwen is the little flying flag.
This is Jiang Chen's motorcycle, right?
Come on.
Please wear the helmet.
Are you ready?
The great escape.
Where's my motorcycle?
Jiang Chen
You're going to
take me for a ride on this bike?
Yes.
Look,
it's a lovely day.
This beautiful bike
suits you very well.
Come on.
No, it's a shame.
You have a really good appearance.
But why are you so melodramatic?
Come on.
Or I'll leave.
Why do you call me melodramatic?
All right.
It's too late.
Do it.
Goodbye.
Ding Xian
Go for it.
The competition is in proposition mode.
Please choose one of the three topics
of youth, family affection and striving
to draw.
What did you draw?
This is my secret.
All right.
Anyway, winning a prize
won't be difficult for you.
Actually, the result is not important.
I suddenly understood what you told me earlier
during the competition today.
You said that
many seemingly ordinary things
will eventually come together
and
have different meanings again.
Now I think
painting
is not just a hobby
for me.
Anyway,
thank you today.
Release.
Spike score.
Ding Juncong, add five points, victory.
Defeat.
Ding Juncong
He is not a schoolboy,
but a demon child definitely.
I don't care. Do my homework for me.
Otherwise, I will tell mother about it.
Mom.
What time is it now?
I'm done.
My mother will be back soon.
What should I do?
Let me help you with your homework.
Clean up quickly.
-Which one?  -This.
Why are there so many people?
Hello, aunt and uncle.
You guys...
We are a study group.
Zhou Siyue is teaching Juncong to do his homework.
Right.
That's nice.
Show me your homework.
Not bad.
You finished your homework very well today.
How did you solve this problem?
This...
Didn't Zhou Siyue teach you just now?
You forgot?
I know you.
So many
brothers and sisters tutor you.
Why don't you seize the opportunity
to learn from them?
Copy this question
into the notebook
and do it again later.
Just stay here.
I will cook for you.
Wait.
It doesn't matter.
We gotta go.
Goodbye, uncle.
Goodbye, auntie.
My mom called me.
How is it?
Be careful this week.
Beware of bad guy.
Who is the bad guy?
Ding Xian
Just come to me.
You did something wrong again?
No.
This is too accurate, right?
How are you?
He scolded you?
It's all right.
What the hell?
Xianxian, you're wonderful.
You are really a great painter.
Look, Xianxian won the first place.
Great job, Little Monster.
You are great, Ding Xian.
Give it to me.
You are like crazy people.
Can you guys be more mature?
How are you?
I'm fine.
A marinated egg, please.
Come on.
Today is Ding Xian's treat.
I will order some unordered
and expensive ones.
Why do you take advantage of everyone?
I just wanna
thank you all very much today.
Without you guys,
I wouldn't have been able to go to the competition.
Song Ziqi is right.
I'll order more too.
Just do it.
You've ordered so much, but you still order?
I can't?
You can.
Can we eat it all?
Are you guys that hungry?
We can definitely eat it all.
You're like a greedy hungry ghost.
You've made me poorer by eating at my house these days.
You argued with your father again?
What is the reason this time?
This time it's different.
A little bit serious.
So I just wanna...
He just wants to be a soldier, but his father
won't allow it.
You're the only one with a mouth.
You will say it sooner or later anyway.
I'll order.
Here's the menu.
Don't talk with me.
I've made up my mind.
I won't advise you.
You told me you wanted to be a soldier when you were eight.
Have you forgotten?
I told you at that time that
if you were a soldier,
I would engage in national defense research.
This is equivalent to
defending our country together.
I haven't forgotten.
We must not go back on our word.
Keep your word.
OK.
Don't worry.
We're with you.
It seems that there is nothing to eat.
Let's go back.
Everyone has a dream.
My dream is to be a pilot.
If you wanna be a pilot,
I will be a flight attendant.
I wanna graduate before you.
I will fly before you.
Clumsy birds have to start flying early.
You call me a clumsy bird?
I'm a clumsy bird.
What about you?
What do you want to do in the future?
Have you finished ordering?
So I'll call the boss.
Please.
I'm coming.
Yes, I want these.
OK.
Did you just order that French Toast?
Yes.
Yes?
Right.
What is
my dream?
His father is a soldier.
Why doesn't he support Jiang Chen?
Jiang Chen
had a bad relationship with his father since he was a child.
He doesn't always
listen to his father.
So his father thinks that he can't endure hardship
and is not suitable for being a soldier.
And you don't know Jiang Chen very well.
That boy
is stubborn.
He is sure to stick to it.
What is on your mind?
I feel that you all have dreams
and goals.
You are great.
You just won the first prize.
Why do you think so much?
Painting is just
one of my hobbies.
Dreams should
be grand.
All dreams
begin with hobbies.
And I believe
you can do anything
you want.
Hobbies.
I wanna be a painter.
It's not easy.
Ding Xian, why don't you sleep?
Right away.
How are you?
I shouldn't have stayed up all night.
Why do I feel like you're dying?
Don't talk nonsense.
You certainly don't understand the pain during the period.
I don't wanna understand either.
It's too torturing.
Don't go to this physical education class.
Where did you get this?
The infirmary.
Let's go.
Xianxian, I gotta go.
You're awake?
Why are you back?
It's too hot outside.
I don't wanna have class.
Zhou Siyue
Have you always wanted to go to Huaqing University?
Why do you suddenly ask this?
After you told me that day,
I've been thinking about it since I got home.
You said to start with interest.
I think since I like painting,
I will become a painter.
But
I didn't learn to draw systematically.
I can't take it for granted.
Why do you smile?
I'm thinking about this very seriously.
I shouldn't smile.
Actually, I think
it's good to be realistic sometimes.
For example,
I always wanna be admitted into Huaqing University.
Actually, I just wanna
go to a bigger place
to test my ability.
It's that simple?
Yes.
Dream.
Goal.
In fact, it just
gives us
a driving force to move forward.
So
is it a dream for me to wanna do well in the exam?
Why are you laughing again?
I wanna say
this dream of yours
can actually be a little bit bigger.
Then get into a key university.
This is the first step I want to take.
Everyone thinks that
I can only get into an ordinary university at most.
But I think about it.
I'm still unconvinced.
I can also be admitted into a key university.
Well.
Let me help you.
You can take a nap again.
When you wake up, let me help you with your test paper.
Otherwise, if I speak now, you can't listen
and you can't remember anything.
Just sleep.
Zhang Haojie
Tang Jiamin
It seems that you did well in the exam.
Safe.
It's impossible for you to fail the exam with my guidance.
Our class
ranks first in the whole grade
this time.
But
I think many people
have begun to be overconfident.
Song Ziqi
You are not going into your senior year of high school soon.
You've already been seniors in high school now .
Xianxian
Make-up classes
will begin immediately after the summer break.
Don't forget to camp together.
The last carnival of the senior year.
So don't go too far.
Please put your heart on your study.
Got it?
I'm back.
Xianxian, look who's here.
Xianxian
Hello.
Why are you here?
I'm on holiday, so I come to see you.
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
Mom
Let me discuss something with you.
Kong Shadi asked me
if I wanted to
hang out with her next week.
I wanna talk to you...
You can't.
Mom, it's the last summer vacation.
It is because this is the last summer vacation
that I disagree.
Where are you going?
We agreed to go camping.
Is it
next to the museum?
Auntie, this is the last holiday.
Shen Hai High School students are really stressful.
It's good to relax at this time.
I also hung out at that time.
But it didn't affect my grades.
You're not like her.
She's different.
It happens that some of our college classmates
are going there, too.
We will take care of them.
You can rest assured.
Mom, just let me go.
I'll only play in this last summer vacation.
Mom
All right.
But you must focus on study after you get back.
OK.
Thank you, mom.
Well, take your time and I'll cook.
Auntie, let me give you a hand.
I'm so looking forward to
this last summer.
Hello.
Xianxian
He's so handsome.
He has been even more handsome since he graduated.
You bring so many things.
Hello.
I've heard a lot about you.
You must be Zhou Siyue.
I know you.
I grew up with Xianxian.
She's told me about you.
This is a war, let's get out of it.
Let's go.
Where shall I put this first?
There you are.
Let me take it over for you.
It doesn't matter.
I'll do it.
Let's go.
Xianxian
We're going to have a campfire dinner later.
Do you want to join us?
OK.
Let's play together.
You guys get ready first.
I'll meet you later.
OK.
See you later.
Let's go.
Why do I feel that
he is getting more and more handsome?
I feel that he is still like that.
Maybe it's because
you grew up with him.
You already know him well.
Anyway, I think
he is more handsome after going to college.
Do you
want to meet him?
I'll be too shy if I go by myself.
Please introduce him to me.
I feel that
even the air is sweet where he is.
Song Ziqi
Why do you take mine?
It's too late.
Don't catch me.
This is not very tasty.
Why do you steal food too?
What's up?
You and Kong Shadi chat about Su Bocong
so fascinating.
So you neglect it.
I don't.
I've seen it all.
You are so childish.
Me?
Stop chasing me.
I can't run anymore.
-It's your fault for eating my food.  -I'm sorry.
By the way.
I solved that problem last night by myself.
You're great.
What about that last function problem?
That's too much.
Please don't talk about studies when playing.
We don't ask you to listen.
I don't want to listen.
Let me take you to the sunset.
Wait a minute.
Was there a function
in the last question last night?
Isn't it a special training for solid geometry?
The one you are talking about
is the 18th set of special training, right?
Our homework is the 18th set of exam papers.
Kong Shadi
Did you memorize the papers I asked you to memorize correctly?
Yes, the 18th set.
Which one of the 18th set?
Are you crazy?
Isn't that the 18th set?
He's funny.
Where are we going?
Don't we watch the sunset?
Printing shop.
You remember the paper wrong.
The new semester will start the day after tomorrow.
Oh.
Last year.
Right.
Jiangsu University.
Thank you.
C.
Because this one plus this one
equals 16, so 16/3.
So it's (16*π)/3.
-Draw another one on this one.  -Xianxian
They say they are going to have a bonfire dance later.
Do you want to join us?
OK.
The bonfire dance is great.
Let's do it together.
Can you dance?
No, but you can teach me.
You
shouldn't mind, right?
Right.
Let's go.
Let's dance together.
Go away.
Are you happy today?
Yes.
It's beautiful here.
Let's dance together.
How to dance?
Left and right.
Friends
We have a custom here.
Dancing around a bonfire
can make our relationship better and better.
So let's all
dance around the bonfire, okay?
OK.
OK, let's hold hands.
Come on.
Hand in hand.
Please
hold hands, okay?
Right.
You sing very well.
What is this?
You lost your diary.
So I
made a small website in my spare time.
It is similar to Blog.
But it doesn't need to be connected to the network.
So what you want to say
can be written on it.
No one else can see it.
You are great.
This is a very basic operation.
It can be used as a small reward for doing well on your exams.
I like it very much, thanks.
I actually
lied at that time.
What?
I said at that time that
my dream was to be admitted into a key university.
Actually, I don't really think so.
At that time, I always thought about
what kind of person I want to be
and what dreams I have.
Then
I didn't know why I thought of you.
I don't mean anything else.
I...
I just think you're good.
Not only do you study well
and care for others,
but you also have a sense of responsibility.
It hit me that
if only I could be
such a good person.
So at that time, my dream was
to become a better person.
But you know I'm not smart.
I don't know where to start.
After careful consideration,
I think I should just
start with the petty things as you said.
I should study hard first,
then go to a key university
and stick to painting.
If there's a chance...
Do you also think I'm stupid?
No.
You're right.
To be a better person,
you must first go to a wider
and bigger place.
At least I think so.
And
you're on that path now.
You
won a prize in the painting competition.
After you chose science,
your record was also increased.
You are now...
I also got to know you.
I used to be very introverted.
I didn't have many friends either.
I didn't know how to get along with people.
Anyway, I think
it's great
to have Ziqi, Shadi
and you.
You're actually pretty good.